[BLACK FRIDAY EARLY ACCESS \[CLICK HERE TO CHECK IT OUT\] BLACK FRIDAY EARLY ACCESS \[CHECK IT OUT\]](https://rockykanaka.com/pages/black-friday-early-access-sign-up)

Free Shipping on Orders Over $79 (USA)

* Treats

* Collections

 Search our site  

Clear[Log in](https://rockykanaka.com/account/login) Cart

Privacy Policy
==============

The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

1. **Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

For example, you may need to provide the following information:

* Name
* Website URL information
* Email address
* Home and business phone number

In addition to providing the foregoing information, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

2. **Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed and designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity.

**Third Party Pixels and Cookies:**

When you visit our website, log in, register or open an email, cookies, ad beacons, and similar technologies may be used by our online data partners or vendors to associate these activities with information they or others have about you, including your email address. We (or service providers on our behalf) may then send communications and marketing to these email addresses. You may opt out of receiving this advertising by emailing support@rockykanaka.com

**What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users' browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers.

Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We utilize encryption/security best practices to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.

**Communication Opt Out**

If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from

The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

1. **Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

For example, you may need to provide the following information:

* Name
* Website URL information
* Email address
* Home and business phone number

In addition to providing the foregoing information, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

2. **Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed and designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity.

**What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users' browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers.

Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We utilize encryption/security best practices to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.

**Communication Opt Out**

If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from RockyKanaka.com, you can unsubscribe by following the opt-out instructions in the emails that they send you located at the footer of the communication.  You can email us at support@rockykanaka.com with questions, comments or suggestions.

**Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?**

We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

**What about Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein.

**SMS/MMS MOBILE MESSAGING MARKETING PROGRAM**

We respect your privacy. We will only use information you provide through the Program to transmit your mobile messages and respond to you, if necessary. This includes, but is not limited to, sharing information with platform providers, phone companies, and other vendors who assist us in the delivery of mobile messages.  WE DO NOT SELL, RENT, LOAN, TRADE, LEASE, OR OTHERWISE TRANSFER FOR PROFIT ANY PHONE NUMBERS OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE PROGRAM TO ANY THIRD PARTY. Nonetheless, We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, to avoid liability, or to protect Our rights or property. When you complete forms online or otherwise provide Us information in connection with the Program, you agree to provide accurate, complete, and true information. You agree not to use a false or misleading name or a name that you are not authorized to use. If, in Our sole discretion, We believe that any such information is untrue, inaccurate, or incomplete, or you have opted into the Program for an ulterior purpose, We may refuse you access to the Program and pursue any appropriate legal remedies.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users of the Program that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of the information you provide through the Program to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please contact us at the following address:

RockyKanaka.com - support@RockyKanaka.com

This Privacy Policy is strictly limited to the Program and has no effect on any other privacy policy(ies) that may govern the relationship between you and Us in other contexts.

You can unsubscribe by following the opt-out instructions in the emails that they send you located at the footer of the communication. We can be reached by postal mail at 4818 E. 2nd Street Long Beach, CA 90803, or by phone at 310-313-1801. You can email us at support@rockykanaka.com with questions, comments or suggestions.

**Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?**

We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

**What about Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein.

**SMS/MMS MOBILE MESSAGING MARKETING PROGRAM**

We respect your privacy. We will only use information you provide through the Program to transmit your mobile messages and respond to you, if necessary. This includes, but is not limited to, sharing information with platform providers, phone companies, and other vendors who assist us in the delivery of mobile messages.  WE DO NOT SELL, RENT, LOAN, TRADE, LEASE, OR OTHERWISE TRANSFER FOR PROFIT ANY PHONE NUMBERS OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE PROGRAM TO ANY THIRD PARTY. Nonetheless, We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, to avoid liability, or to protect Our rights or property. When you complete forms online or otherwise provide Us information in connection with the Program, you agree to provide accurate, complete, and true information. You agree not to use a false or misleading name or a name that you are not authorized to use. If, in Our sole discretion, We believe that any such information is untrue, inaccurate, or incomplete, or you have opted into the Program for an ulterior purpose, We may refuse you access to the Program and pursue any appropriate legal remedies.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users of the Program that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of the information you provide through the Program to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please contact us at the following address:

RockyKanaka.com- support@rockykanaka.com

This Privacy Policy is strictly limited to the Program and has no effect on any other privacy policy(ies) that may govern the relationship between you and Us in other contexts.

The Details

© 2024, [RockyKanaka](https://rockykanaka.com/). All rights reserved.

Country/region

AFN ؋ EUR € ALL L DZD د.ج EUR € USD $ XCD $ XCD $ USD $ AMD դր. AWG ƒ SHP £ AUD $ EUR € AZN ₼ BSD $ USD $ BDT ৳ BBD $ USD $ EUR € BZD $ XOF Fr USD $ USD $ BOB Bs. BAM КМ BWP P USD $ USD $ USD $ BND $ BGN лв. XOF Fr BIF Fr KHR ៛ XAF Fr CAD $ CVE $ USD $ KYD $ XAF Fr XAF Fr USD $ CNY ¥ AUD $ AUD $ USD $ KMF Fr XAF Fr CDF Fr NZD $ CRC ₡ XOF Fr EUR € ANG ƒ EUR € CZK Kč DKK kr. DJF Fdj XCD $ DOP $ USD $ EGP ج.م USD $ XAF Fr USD $ EUR € USD $ ETB Br FKP £ DKK kr. FJD $ EUR € EUR € EUR € XPF Fr EUR € XOF Fr GMD D USD $ EUR € USD $ GBP £ EUR € DKK kr. XCD $ EUR € GTQ Q GBP £ GNF Fr XOF Fr GYD $ USD $ HNL L HKD $ HUF Ft ISK kr INR ₹ IDR Rp USD $ EUR € GBP £ ILS ₪ EUR € JMD $ JPY ¥ USD $ USD $ KZT 〒 KES KSh USD $ EUR € USD $ KGS som LAK ₭ EUR € LBP ل.ل USD $ USD $ USD $ CHF CHF EUR € EUR € MOP P USD $ MWK MK MYR RM MVR MVR XOF Fr EUR € EUR € USD $ MUR ₨ EUR € USD $ MDL L EUR € MNT ₮ EUR € XCD $ MAD د.م. USD $ MMK K USD $ AUD $ NPR ₨ EUR € XPF Fr NZD $ NIO C$ XOF Fr NGN ₦ NZD $ AUD $ MKD ден USD $ USD $ PKR ₨ ILS ₪ USD $ PGK K PYG ₲ PEN S/. PHP ₱ NZD $ PLN zł EUR € QAR ر.ق EUR € RON Lei USD $ RWF FRw WST T EUR € STD Db SAR ر.س XOF Fr RSD РСД USD $ SLL Le SGD $ ANG ƒ EUR € EUR € SBD $ USD $ USD $ GBP £ KRW ₩ USD $ EUR € LKR ₨ EUR € SHP £ XCD $ XCD $ EUR € EUR € XCD $ USD $ USD $ USD $ SEK kr CHF CHF TWD $ TJS ЅМ TZS Sh THB ฿ USD $ XOF Fr NZD $ TOP T$ TTD $ GBP £ USD $ USD $ USD $ USD $ AUD $ USD $ UGX USh UAH ₴ AED د.إ GBP £ USD $ UYU $ UZS VUV Vt EUR € USD $ VND ₫ XPF Fr MAD د.م. YER ﷼ USD $ USD $

Update country/region

Country/region

United States (USD $)

Menu

Search

Cart

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
